Product

Use Cases

Company

Resources

Our Privacy Policy
==================

Last Reviewed: May 16, 2023.

**1\. INTRODUCTION**

Grain Intelligence, Inc., (“Grain”) and its subsidiaries (collectively, the “Grain” or “we” or “us” or “our”) is committed to protecting the privacy of the individuals who visit our Websites (as herein defined) (“Website Visitors”), who are authorized to use our Services through a Subscriber’s Account (“Users”). For the purposes of this Policy, the term, “Websites”, shall refer collectively to www.Grain.co as well as the other websites that the Grain operates and that link to this Policy, the term “Services” shall refer to our on-demand product excellence system, and tools and services made available from the Websites.

The term “Subscriber” shall refer to an individual or an entity that has agreed to a Service Agreement for use of our Services, including an individual representing the Subscribing company, the term “Account” shall mean all Grain accounts or instances created by or on behalf of Subscriber within the Service.

**2\. SCOPE OF THIS POLICY**

This Policy outlines our handling practices and how we collect and use the Personal Information you provide during your online and offline interactions with us. As used in this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means any information that can be used to individually identify a person, and may include, but is not limited to, name, email address, postal or other physical address, credit or debit card number, title, and other personally identifiable information.

**We may collect, the following categories of Personal Data about you when you use or otherwise interact with our Service:**

* Name
* Title
* Email address
* Home/work/mobile telephone number
* Postal or other physical address
* Credit/debit card information
* IP addresses and other information collected passively such as cookies and tracking technologies (further described below), browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the website and/or Products.
* Device identifiers
* Our servers automatically record certain information when you use the Service, including your IP address, operating system type and version, client version, IP addresses along the network path, and the MAC address of your internet connection.
* We also automatically record information about your usage of the Service, including actions taken, date and time, frequency, duration, quantity, quality, network connectivity, and performance information related to logins, clicks, messages, contacts, content shared, calls, use of video and screen sharing, meetings, cloud recording, and other feature usage information (“Usage Information”)
* Other information you upload, provide, or create while using the Service ("User-Generated Information"), as further detailed in the “User Generated Information” section below

Personal information does not include “Usage Data” which we define as encoded or anonymized information or aggregated data we collect about a group or category of services, features or users which does not contain personally identifying information. Usage Data helps us understand trends in usage of the Service so that we can better consider new features or otherwise tailor the Service. In addition to collecting and using Usage Data ourselves, we may share Usage Data with third parties, including our customers, partners and service providers, for various purposes, including to help us better understand our customers’ needs and improve the Service as well as for advertising and marketing purposes. We do not share Usage Data with third parties in a way that would enable them to identify you personally.

**User-Generated Information**

We collect and retain, Personal Information and other information you upload, provide, or create while using the Service ("User-Generated Information"), including information related to:

* Meeting title, invitation content, participants, meeting link, date, time and duration. We collect activity recorded in the meeting (such as joining or leaving), including activity related to third-party integrations, together with the date, time, person engaged in the activity, and other participants in the meeting with the date, time, duration, and quality ratings that you provide.
* Message content, sender and recipients, date, and time.
* If you use a feature of the Services that allows for recordings, we collect and store information from you that you provide in connection with such use and through such recordings, to the extent you provide it to us. This information may include Personal Information, if you provide us with Personal Information.
* Status information, for example about whether and when you are actively viewing a document.

All messages and content you share in a meeting, including Personal Data about you or others, will be available to all other participants in that meeting.

Our Websites may contain links to other websites and the information practices and the content of such other websites are governed by the privacy statements of such other websites. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any such other websites to understand their information practices.

If you have purchased a subscription to our Services additional terms relating to data rights are set forth in and governed by our Terms of Service, available here: \[[https://www.grain.co/terms](https://www.grain.co/terms)\], or such other applicable agreement between you and any member of the Grain relating to your access to and use of such Services (“Service Agreement”).

We may transfer Personal Information to companies that help us provide our Services to Subscribers.

**3\. INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US**

Account and Registration Information:

If you are Subscriber or User, we ask for and collect Personal Information about you and your Users such as name, address, phone number, email address, and credit card information of the Subscriber, as well as certain related information like Subscriber company name and website name email address and name or alias from each User.

If you sign-up for a free Account, you are not required to enter your credit card information unless and until you decide to continue with a paid subscription to our Services. A third-party intermediary is used to manage credit card processing.

We refer to any information described above as “Account Information” for the purposes of this Policy. By voluntarily providing us with Account Information, you represent that you are the owner of such Personal Information or are otherwise authorized to provide it to us, specifically, if you as a Subscriber provide us Account Information related to the User, you represent that the User has not objected to such processing.

Submissions by the Website Visitor:

We ask for and collect Personal Information from you when you submit web forms on our Websites or as you use interactive features of the Websites, including, participation in surveys, contests, promotions, sweepstakes, requesting customer support, or communicating with us.

**4\. INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT FROM YOU ON OUR WEBSITES**

Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:

We and our authorized partners use cookies and other information gathering technologies for a variety of purposes. These technologies may provide us with Personal Information, information about devices and networks you utilize to access our Websites, and other information regarding your interactions with our Websites.

Web beacons, tags and scripts may be used on our Websites or in email or other electronic communications we send to you. These assist us in delivering cookies, counting visits to our Websites, understanding usage and campaign effectiveness and determining whether an email has been opened and acted upon. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by our third-party service providers on an individual and aggregated basis.

We use Local Storage Objects (“LSOs”) such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our Websites use LSOs such as HTML5 and Flash to collect and store information.

Logs:

As is true with most websites and services delivered over the Internet, we gather certain information and store it in log files when you interact with our Websites and Services. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses as well as browser type, internet service provider, URLs of referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, information you search for, locale and language preferences, identification numbers associated with your devices, your mobile carrier, and system configuration information. Occasionally, we connect Personal Information to information gathered in our log files as necessary to improve our Websites and Services. In such a case, we would treat the combined information in accordance with this Policy.

Analytics:

We collect analytics information when you use the Websites to help us improve them. We may also share anonymous data about your actions on our Websites with third-party service providers of analytics services.

**5\. INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM OTHER SOURCES**

Social Media Widgets:

The Websites include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, and widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our Websites. These features may collect your Internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on the Websites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Websites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the companies that provide them.

Information From Third Party Services:

We may also obtain other information, including Personal Information, from third parties and combine that with information we collect through our Websites. For example, we may have access to certain information from a third party authentication service if you log into our Services through such a service or otherwise provide us with access to information from the service. Any access that we may have to such information from a third party social media or authentication service is in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by that service. By authorizing us to connect with a third party service, you authorize us to access and store your name, email address(es), current city, profile picture URL, and other Personal Information that the third party service makes available to us, and to use and disclose it in accordance with this Policy. You should check your privacy settings on these third party services to understand and change the information sent to us through these services. For example, you can log in to the Services using sign-in services such as Google Authentication, as further described below.

**6\. HOW WE USE INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT**

We use the information we collect about you (including Personal Information, to the extent applicable) to (a) provide, operate, maintain and improve the Services; (b) enable you to access and use the Services; (c) process and complete transactions, and send you related information, including purchase confirmations and invoices; (d) send transactional messages, including responses to your comments, questions, and requests; provide customer service and support; and send you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages; (e) send promotional communications, such as providing you with information about products and services, features, surveys, newsletters, offers, promotions, contests, and events; and provide other news or information about us and our partners; (f) process and deliver contest or sweepstakes entries and rewards; (g) monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with the Websites and Services and for marketing or advertising purposes; (h) investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions, unauthorized access to the Services, and other illegal activities; (i) personalize the Websites and Services, including by providing features or advertisements that match your interests and preferences; and (j) comply with our legal obligations, including our obligations related to personal data protection.

**7\. LEGAL GROUNDS FOR PROCESSING**

We process your information for the purposes described in this Policy, based on the following legal grounds:

(i) When we’re pursuing legitimate interests

We process your information for our legitimate interests and those of third parties. This means that we process your information for things like: Providing, operating; maintaining, and improving our Services; enabling you to access and use the Services; promoting the Services; sending promotional communications, monitoring and analyzing trends, usage, and activities in connection with the Websites and Services; investigating and preventing fraudulent transactions, unauthorized access to the Services, and other illegal activities; (i) personalizing the Websites and Services.

(ii) When we’re providing a service

We process your data to provide a service you’ve asked for under the Service Contract or other contract between you and us. This means that we process your information for things like: Enabling you to access and use the Services; processing transactions, and sending you related information; providing customer service and support; personalizing the Websites and Services.

(iii) When we’re complying with legal obligations

We’ll process your data when we have a legal obligation to do so, for example, if we’re responding to legal process or an enforceable governmental request.

(iv) With your consent

We may ask for your agreement to process your information for specific purposes and you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. For example, we ask for your consent to publish your testimonial, if it includes your identification. If you wish to withdraw your consent, you can contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://grain.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

**8\. SHARING OF INFORMATION COLLECTED**

Third-Party Service Providers:

We share information, including Personal Information, with our third-party service providers that we use to provide hosting for and maintenance of our Websites, application development, backup, storage, payment processing, analytics and other services for us. These third-party service providers may have access to or process your Personal Information for the purpose of providing these services for us. We do not permit our third-party service providers to use the Personal Information that we share with them for their marketing purposes or for any other purpose than in connection with the services they provide to us.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Our Rights:

In certain situations, we may be required to disclose Personal Information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We may disclose Personal Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may also share such information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Service Agreement, or as otherwise required by law.

Grain Sharing:

We may share information, including Personal Information, with any member of the Grain.

With Your Consent:

We may also share Personal Information with third parties when we have your consent to do so.

**9\. CHOICE AND COMMUNICATIONS PREFERENCES**

We offer those who provide personal contact information a means to choose how we use the information provided. You can opt-out of receiving marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of our marketing emails or you may send a request to [\[email protected\]](https://grain.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

**10\. ACCESSING, EXPORTING AND REMOVING YOUR INFORMATION AND OTHER AVAILABLE RIGHTS**

Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold and otherwise process, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your Personal Information. To request this information please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://grain.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Subscribers to our Services may update or change their Account Information by editing their profile or organization record or by contacting [\[email protected\]](https://grain.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) for more detailed instructions. To make a request to have Personal Information maintained by us returned to you or removed, please email [\[email protected\]](https://grain.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Requests to access, change, or remove your information will be handled within thirty 30 days.

An individual who seeks access to, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccuracies in Personal Information stored or processed by us on behalf of a Subscriber should direct his/her query to the Subscriber (the data controller). Upon receipt of a request from one of our Subscribers for us to remove the data, we will respond to their request within thirty (30) days. We will retain Personal Information that we store and process on behalf of our Subscribers for as long as needed to provide the Services to our Subscribers. We will retain and use this Personal Information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

If you are a Subscriber or otherwise provide us with Personal Information in connection with your use of our Websites or Services, we will delete this information upon your request, provided that, notwithstanding such request, this information may be retained for as long as you maintain an account for our Services, or as needed to provide you with our Services (in particular for Accounts with multiple Users where we need to retain the interaction with Users who continue to use the Services), comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

**12\. SECURITY**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We follow generally accepted, reasonable, and appropriate standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. In deciding what is reasonable and appropriate we take into account the risks involved and the nature of the information. If you have any questions about the security of your Personal Information, you can contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://grain.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

**13\. CHILDREN’S PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 16. If you are under the age of 16, please do not use or submit any Personal Information through our Websites or Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Information through the Websites or Services without parental permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 16 has provided Personal Information to us through the Websites or Services, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://grain.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to delete that information.

**14\. BUSINESS TRANSACTIONS**

We may assign or transfer this Policy, as well as your account and related information and data, including any Personal Information, to any person or entity that acquires all or substantially all of our business, stock or assets, or with whom we merge.

**15\. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

If there are any material changes to this Policy, you will be notified by our posting of a prominent notice on Our Website. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Your continued use of the Websites or the Services constitutes your agreement to be bound by such changes to this Policy. Your only remedy, if you do not accept the terms of this Policy, is to discontinue use of the Websites and the Services.

**16\. CONTACT US**

If you have questions regarding this Policy or about the privacy practices of Grain, please contact us by email at [\[email protected\]](https://grain.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), or at:

Grain Intelligence, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Officer

250 N 100 W

Unit #103

Provo, UT 84601

‍
-

Get Started with Grain
----------------------

[\[email protected\]](https://grain.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Product

Use Cases

Company

[\[email protected\]](https://grain.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Resources

#### Subscribe to our newsletter

Get monthly email updates about the improvements and roadmaps we might change

Thank you! Your submission has been received!

Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.

© 2024 Grain Intelligence Inc. All rights reserved.
